# Jens Henrik Vogelius

Age 40, Danish

Ydingvej 40 8752 Østbirk Denmark ☐ +45 51787606 ☑ jenshenrik.skuldbol@gmail.com

## Knowledge Areas

Programming C#.NET, Java, Python, AngularJS, React, SQL

Development Git, Docker, CICD, Azure, Agile, Testing

### Work Experience

2022 — **Senior software developer**, *Mjølner Informatics*, Silkeborg/Århus Change of employer due to Norlys' acquisition of Mjølner Informatics. Continuing same project from my time at Norlys.

2021–2022 **Software Developer**, *Norlys*, Silkeborg

Developing a custom order management system designed to plan and manage the daily work of 200+ electricians doing various tasks, including maintenance, cable mapping and establishing new parts of the electrical network. A React web app scaled for desktop and tablet running on top of .NET microservices with integrations to ERP, GIS and route planning systems. *Main learnings: GIS domain knowledge, Azure, Microservices, Project Management.* 

- 2020–2021 **Software developer**, *Isobar*, Århus Continuing work from my time at e2y.
- 2019–2020 **Software developer**, *e2y*, Århus

Developing a SAP Cloud Commerce (formerly Hybris) solution for a reseller of aircraft spareparts. *Main learnings: Java/Spring, SAP Cloud Commerce.* 

2016–2019 **Software developer**, Vertica, Århus

Developing ecommerce solutions for various customers, including Sanistål, Vestas, and Coop Main learnings: Episerver and Umbraco development, ecommerce domain knowledge.

- 2014–2016 **Senior software developer**, *IT Minds*, Copenhagen Fulltime employee following graduation. Mostly same Episerver project.
- 2012–2014 Part time software developer, IT Minds, Copenhagen

Multiple projects of varying size in a wide range of languages, including Java, C#, ASP 2.0 and PHP. A larger Episerver project involving a fully customized webshop for selling TV subscriptions. Includes 6 months of fulltime internship required for BA degree. *Main learnings: Customer relations, general software development.* 

#### Education

2007–2009 **2 years of Ba. studies**, *Copenhagen University*, Copenhagen - Denmark, *Computer Science* 

2010–2014 Ba.Eng in IT, DTU, Lyngby - Denmark, Computer Science

Languages

Danish Native

English Fluent
German Pretty rusty

#### About me

I am a technically curious software developer with 10+ years of professional experience. I enjoy expanding my horizon whether that would be learning a new language, using a new tool, or tackling an unknown domain. Professional growth is a huge motivator in my day to day work life.

I firmly believe in using the right tool for the job at hand, that testing is a core part of software development and that the best solutions are crafted through dialog and sparring. The importance of semantics is a pet peeve of mine.

I live in Østbirk, near Skanderborg, with my wife and our two children, ages 8 and 6. In my spare time I enjoy playing board games, brewing beer, and dabbling in game development.